Guide to the Joseph W. Gordon, Deputy Dean of Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Joseph W. Gordon, Deputy Dean of Yale College, records
1828-2014
1953-2014
RU 1141
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1
The collection contains the records of Joseph W. Gordon, Deputy Dean of Yale College and Dean of Undergraduate Edcuation. Includes administrative files which consist of reports, meeting notes and materials, and reports with supporting materials.
Yale College (1887- ). Dean's Office
Gordon, Joseph Wayne
General Note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-B (YRG 9-B), Records of deputy, associate, and assistant deans of Yale College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains the records of Joseph W. Gordon, Deputy Dean of Yale College and Dean of Undergraduate Edcuation. Includes administrative files which consist of reports, meeting notes and materials, and reports with supporting materials.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by accession.
Yale College (1887- ). Dean's Office
- Records, 1828-2014; 1953-2014; Accession 2016-A-018
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 1, 2048.
  - Academic integrity, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accounting, 2011-2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AEA summer minority program, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arts appointments, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol and other drugs, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AYA Alumni Survey, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AYA Assembly, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Arabic, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Center for Language Study, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - College seminar review, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Committee planning, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dean's annual report, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Education, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Education studies, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Environmental studies, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences departmental trends, 1977-1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Faculty meeting bylaws-Yale, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Faculty meeting bylaws-other universities, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Fieldwork and Yale College classes meeting, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Field trip-academic, 2011-2012 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Field trips, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Foreign language and distance learning, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Freshman affairs, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Global affairs, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Grading, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Graduate and professional student housing, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Handbook for university staff, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Learning Collaborative on High-Risk Drinking (Box 1, Folder 29a)
  - LGBT studies, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Liberal education essays (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Models of student-faculty interactions: Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - New residential colleges, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Online course evaluations, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Pre-registration orientation, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Proposed operating budget, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Students of concern policy, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Student information systems, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - University's response in event of death/serious injury, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 40a)
  - Women at Yale statistical profile, 1969-1979 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Workplace survey, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Writing Center (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Yale Faculty Handbook, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Yale Aids Memorial Project (YAMP), 2012 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Yale College reports
    - Ad-Hoc Committee on Faculty Appointments, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Appendix to the Future of the College and Graduate School, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Comments on Committee on Yale College Education (CYCE) Report for reference, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - College Criteria Study-notes, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Committee on the Future of Residential Colleges, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Committee on Education, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Course of Study Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - CYCE Progress Report, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Faculty Committee, 1828 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Freshman Year: Observations and Criticisms, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Future of the College and Graduate School, 1957-1976 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Hall Committee, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Institute of Social Science, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - President's Committee on General Education, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Senior Study, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Social Science Planning Initiative-Engineering and Applied Science, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Status of Minority Students, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Study Committee, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Study Group on Yale College, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Study Group on New Residential Colleges, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Yale-National University of Singapore (NUS) Advisory Committee, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 66)